International Labor Organization (ILO) Documents 5721
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Labor Organization (ILO) Documents
1956-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Labor Organization (ILO)
5721
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5698072
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 19, 2003
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6116m: David L. Cole Report on "Conscious Promotion in Practice of Better Labor-Management Cooperation"
Labor movement -- United States; International Labour Organisation
5698072
- "Johnson Committee Report, Background Information." (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1 binder, unpaged
- Photocopies of documents "copied from the David A. Morse Papers in the Princeton University Library" (Box 1, Folder 2)
  includes notes, memos, correspondence, meeting minutes most of which are marked "confidential."
- "The U.S. and the I.L.O.", 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Bureau of International Labor Affairs, Sept. 78, 82 p.
- "Report on the 63rd Session of the International Labor Conference, Geneva, June 1-22, 1977." (Box 1, Folder 3)
  June 1-22 1977; 46 p. plus appendices (Prepared by the Bureau of International Labor Affairs)
- "Labor Standards and Trade Distortions", 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Sept. 1, 1978. 21 p.
- "Johnson Committee Report, Introduction" (Box 1, Folder 4)
  46 p.
- "Tripartitism in the International Labor Organization" prepared by Dept. of State-Commerce-Labor ILR Review Staff Group-Lawyer, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Aug. 16, 1956, 38 p. plus appendices
- "A Report to the Assistant Secretary of State for International Organization Affairs on the International Labor Organization and the National Policy of the U.S." by John T. Fishburn, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  73 p. ("Limited Official Use")
- "The U.S. and the ILO: The Problem and A Plan of Action, An Interagency Report on the Participation of the U.S. in the International Labor Organization,", 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Feb. 16, 1971, "confidential" 80 p. plus appendices and attachments
- Miscellaneous documents re "Outline of ILO Study" (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "Admission of the PLO As Observer at ILO Conferences -Chronology, 1974-75,", 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  June 1975, 9 p.
- "ILO Machinery for Promoting Human Rights", 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  8 p. mimeo